

ABOUT ME

I'm a junior game programmer specialized on object-oriented programming. Although I at my fourth year of university, I have already done a great variety of projects on my own, won several awards, done over 13 game jams and worked for two videogame companies. I'm a very enterprising person, outgoing and eager for new experiences.

CONTACT

636 98 24 40

Mataró, Barcelona

marina.chava24@gmail.com

Nationality: Spanish & Australian

Date of birth: 13/12/2000

Gender: Female

LINKS

Portfolio:

https://marinachavarria.netlify.app/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/marinachavarria-gonzalez/

Marina Chavarria Gonzalez

Junior game programmer

WORK EXPERIENCE

MELBOT STUDIOS Jan. 2021 – Now

I work for Melbot as a junior programmer. Melbot is a videogame company that combines art and innovation to make games with a soul.

INTERSHIP AT KANEDA GAMES SL Jun. 2021 – Aug. 2021

I work for 3 months for unpublish project. I was with a programming team following their coding conventions, making physics, player controllers, AI, and making the game structure all the way from the menus to the game modes.

XNERGIC TECNOCAMPUS Oct. 2020 – Jan. 2021

I worked with Xnergic, a company which gives different technology curses during the year to children. I have done all the way from Unity and C# to Arduino.

PROJECTS

IT HAS TO BE YOU | UNITY GAME

July 2021

- Narrative puzzle for my third year final project.
- All the team work for three months to make the game. We did different puzzles systems and also an inventory system.

CUBE'S SIDE! | UNITY MOBILE GAME

September 2021

- A puzzle game with two game modes, one with linear levels and the other one with randomly generated levels.
- The game was created only by myself with Unity, and it has an Ads system and a progress saving system.

Over 10 games more on my Itch.io

GAME AWARDS

CAECUS King Game Jam

Overall best game – 2019

BABY KING IndieDevDay Game Jam

Honourable mention – 2020

CODEBOX

Siemens Gamesa Hackathon

Second place - 2020

WORLD CLASSATE

Siemens Gamesa Hackathon

First place – 2021

FORMATION

VIDEOGAME DESIGN | TECNOCAMPUS

2018 - Currently studying

Im currently on my forth year studying videogames design at Tecnocampus Mataro.

LANGUAGES

English: High

Spanish: Native

Catalan: Native

SKILLS

- C#
- Lua
- Unity

- Defold R
- Unreal engine